<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>esaleatorio.com</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on esaleatorio.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A list of resources to build better emails</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642392/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642392/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://github.com/jonathandion/awesome-emails
Join GitHub today GitHub is home to over 36 million developers working together to host and review code, manage projects, and build software together.
Sign up</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Plus will launch November for $6.99</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642404/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642404/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://www.polygon.com/2019/4/11/17461766/disney-plus-price-release-date-shows-marvel-star-wars-pixar
In the age of exclusive streaming services like HBO GO and CBS All Access sitting amongst streaming giants like Netflix or Hulu, it’s no surprise that the Walt Disney Company is putting together a streaming service of its own. Disney Plus will draw upon the brand’s vast reservoir of content, and finally, we know when it will launch: November 12, 2019.
Disney Plus is being priced very aggressively — $6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney&#43; Streaming Service Launches (Available Nov 12)</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642420/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642420/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://www.engadget.com/2019/04/11/disney-plus/
Content As we knew, Captain Marvel will be a streaming exclusive on Disney+ from day one, and the company said all of the Cars movies will be there also. Disney also showed off the Falcon &amp;amp; Winter Soldier spinoff show we&amp;rsquo;d heard about, and revealed a new show from Jeff Goldblum produced by National Geographic that&amp;rsquo;s in development. Frozen 2 will be a streaming exclusive by the time it comes home next, and the first one, along with the rest of Disney&amp;rsquo;s Signature movies will be streaming on day one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focussed Workflows for Your Projects</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642330/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642330/</guid>
      <description> Story source:
https://matterbase.io
&amp;ldquo;I have always found calendars to be too structured and disconnected for my own liking.What I needed was a place where I could jot down ideas, notes and tasks that are event related, without having to switch between apps.This is why I decided to build Matterbase&amp;rdquo;
- Hermann (Maker) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GE Aviation and the Ceramic Matrix Composite Revolution</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642358/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642358/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=is1BBilkyUM
GE Aviation is creating adjacent factories in Huntsville, Alabama, to mass- produce silicon carbide (SiC) materials used to manufacture ceramic matrix composite components (CMCs) for jet engines and land-based gas turbines.
For more than 20 years, scientists at GE’s Global Research Centers and GE’s industrial businesses have worked to develop CMCs. In recent years, GE Aviation has made significant strides in advancing CMCs for jet propulsion.
Learn how GE is bringing the future of flight to today¹s aircraft when you subscribe to the GE Aviation Channel at youtube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaia Hypothesis</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642354/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642354/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gaia_hypothesis
Hypothesis that living organisms interact with their surroundings in a self- regulating system

The study of planetary habitability is partly based upon extrapolation from knowledge of the
Earth
&amp;rsquo;s conditions, as the Earth is the only planet currently known to harbour life.
The Gaia hypothesis ( , , ), also known as the Gaia theory or the Gaia principle , proposes that living organisms interact with their inorganic surroundings on Earth to form a synergistic and self-regulating, complex system that helps to maintain and perpetuate the conditions for life on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Bad Is Your Colormap? (2014)</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642379/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642379/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://jakevdp.github.io/blog/2014/10/16/how-bad-is-your-colormap/
If you want to take a step toward joining the in-crowd of chromatically- sensitive data viz geeks, your best bet is to start by bashing jet. Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t know it by name, I can guarantee that if you&amp;rsquo;ve read many scientific papers, you&amp;rsquo;ve seen jet before. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s a snapshot of a plot from neuroscience journal which is skewered by an appropriately ranty blogpost on the subject:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the digital age, cognitive biases are running wild</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642365/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642365/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://hackernoon.com/in-the-digital-age-cognitive-biases-are-running-wild-420b8f4f7cb5
How the Internet Amplifies Our Cognitive Biases Photo by jesse orrico on Unsplash
Here are three strange ways the human mind works:  If a person with a certain strong belief is presented with clear evidence of the belief being false, this may lead to a reinforcement of the belief. A person might draw different conclusions from the same type of information depending on in what way the information is being presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Still Emulation: Saving Video Game History Before It&#39;s Too Late</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642369/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642369/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://gdcvault.com/play/1025782/It-s-Still-Emulation-Saving
Please enter search word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Perf Little Book</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642445/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642445/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://github.com/NanXiao/perf-little-book
Linux perf little book When talking about perf in Linux, it actually refers to 2 things:
a) Perf_events (also be called as perf for short): a subsystem which was merged into Linux kernel since 2.6.31;
b) A powerful and comprehensive user-space tool: perf, which leverages perf_events subsystem to do performance analysis.
Perf is a really powerful tool. As Brendan Greeg wrote in his Choosing a Linux Tracer (2015):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McDonald&#39;s in Taiwan to stop providing plastic straws by July</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642440/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642440/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
http://focustaiwan.tw/news/asoc/201904110018.aspx
Photo for illustrative purposes only / CNA file photo Taipei, April 11 (CNA) Fast food company McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said Thursday that it will no longer offer plastic straws at its restaurants in Taiwan, with effect from July, in accordance with a government initiative to reduce the use of plastic.
At a press conference, the company said it is phasing in the new plan, starting Friday, by not proactively offering plastic straws at its checkout counters, the company said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Prismo Data Loss</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642438/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://fediverse.blog/~/Prismo/on-prismo-data-loss
Sooooo - it happened. Nightmare of all the developers on this planet. Entire production database of prismo.news has been accidentally wiped out and it was fully my fault. In this article, i&amp;rsquo;m gonna try to analyze what happened, how i got here and what can i do to prevent such stuff from happening ever again. This post is gonna be totally technical so if you don’t care or don’t have time to read that, long story short is - make damn sure your backups are properly configured!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powering the Xiaomi Mobile with TiDB</title>
      <link>/posts/post-19642405/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/post-19642405/</guid>
      <description>Story source:
https://pingcap.com/success-stories/tidb-in-xiaomi/
Industry: Consumer Electronics
Authors: Liang Zhang (DBA team leader at Xiaomi), Youfei Pan (DBA at Xiaomi), and Biwen Wang (Software engineer at Xiaomi)
Xiaomi is a leading consumer electronics and software company and the fourth-largest smartphone manufacturer in the world, with market-leading positions in both China and India.
MIUI (MI User Interface) is a mobile operating system developed by Xiaomi, based on Google’s Android operating system. It supports various Xiaomi services and customized apps, such as Themes, Music, and its own App Store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two</title>
      <link>/posts/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 15:57:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/two/</guid>
      <description>We know that this works, It is time to check if this theme works on the build with AWS old Ubuntu 14.04 image. The Ubuntu image was recently updated this month of May 2019 to 18.04LTS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One</title>
      <link>/posts/one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 15:53:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/one/</guid>
      <description>This is one I am adding information to this file ONE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test3</title>
      <link>/posts/test3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 13:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/test3/</guid>
      <description>This will be it!! Success or keep working. Test3</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>